

# **UMUT KAAN ÖZDEMIR**

#### Computer Scientist, Game Developer

y01cu.github.io

@ umutaan50@gmail.com

in umut-kaan-özdemir-501032203

v01cu

**J** +905514259473 Ankara, Türkive

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a committed Computer Scientist and Game Developer with nearly three years of experience. My latest project, a game now available on Google Play, highlights my skills in creating engaging digital experiences.

A lifelong gamer, I have the potential to bring both passion and technical expertise to the table. I am excited about the opportunity to collaborate with Company X's team, contributing to innovative projects and driving the future of gaming and interactive techonologies.

### LANGUAGES

Turkish: Native

English: Advanced / C1

### REFERENCES

Öner Önçer - Onivo Games: Owner

- in oner-oncer-413391161
- ✓ oneroncer@gmail.com

Filiz Koçoğlu - Doctoral Thesis Writer

- in filiz-koçoğlu-2349ab121

Ridvan Bal - Mayadem: Developer

- in ridvan-bal-2b144862
- bal.rdvn@gmail.com

# TECH STACK

Unity: VR/Mobile/PC



.NET

WebGL Git

GLSL

Blender

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Indie Game Developer - Onivo Games

i 10.2023 - Still

Ankara, Türkiye (Remote)

- I have developed our arcade idle mobile game in our two people team. Handled Firebase Analytics, Facebook Ads, Google Admob, Google IAP, In app update. Used navmesh system for helper agents. Implemented a proper data save system and made the game easily scalable for future development.
- Link of the game ->  **Gained 148 installed audience in two weeks.**

Unity Developer - Doctoral Thesis

**1** 09.2022 - Still

Ankara, Türkiye (Remote)

• Updated ALCO-VR project for the current state of VR for a doctoral thesis. Changed it's language and added a Turkish equivalent "meyhane" scene. Implementing the project in Meta Quest 3 right now.

Internship - Mayadem | 🏶

**1** 08.2022 - 09.2022

Ankara, Türkiye (Remote)

• Developed a 2D puzzle platformer game using Unity Engine. Implemented a relatively complex player controller that can climb, inventory system. Used custom animation rigging and sprite shapes.

Internship - Enoks | 🌐

**=** 07.2021 - 08 2021

Ankara, Türkiye (In-Office)

• Updated their, reporting system software that had a connection with excel sheet. Used MSSQL with Visual Studio.

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor's degree, Computer. Eng. | Gazi University, Eng. Fac.

**2019 - 2023** 

Ankara, Türkiye

## **PROJECTS**

All of My Projects | •

• Including 2D, 3D games, my graduation project, my Unity tools, my jam games, and all other projects of mine can be found in my portfolio website. More than 20 projects are sorted considering time spent to them